[{"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "The date of the wedding, can I tell him?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I feared for the worst and hoped for the best.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "I mean were you even remotely surprised at the verdict?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, I think the best way to summarize her is to parrot the testimony that was actually given in the trial.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "How would you summarize her?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Are you -- are you a mother, Dorothy?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think the key word that you just said is rational.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "But can you honestly imagine anybody that you knew who's a mother ever behaving like that?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "I believe that this was an accident that snowballed out of control.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is that what you personally believe?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I am concerned for her.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Are you concerned about her ability to lead a free life in relative safety?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, I went into the case, I was asked to come and donate my time for free, to work on this case, to work on the science aspect.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Do you want to clarify it?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, I think before you determine someone is a risk, you have to take the time to understand them.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, the responses that I've gotten back from the people that have experienced trauma, actually, there were several responses that talked about situations where they pretended the individual in their life had not really died.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "I mean, have you ever heard of or been involved with any case like this in your life where a mother has not reported a child missing for over 30 days?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I'm alive, yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "You can confirm you're alive?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "My response was, you know, it happened to Mark Twain so I simply quoted Mark Twain's comment that rumors of his demise were exaggerated.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Was it a bit disconcerting?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that is the number one question.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I think that's a very valid question.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "I mean, what do you say to the skeptics who said this was never ever had a chance?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, the previous weekend.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "When was the exact moment you knew that she was not going to go through with the wedding?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "On Sunday night.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "When did you find out that she was doing that?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I think an argument could be made that she took me for a ride.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "I mean do you think that she took you for a ride?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yes, but not as much as she would have if she'd married me.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Has she got any money out of this?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, she asked for a Bentley right before we split.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "I mean how much has she walked away with?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "The ring was -- I'm not sure exactly.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "How much was the ring?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "A little but not a great deal.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "On top?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "That there's more that we don't know.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "What is your -- you're a smart guy, what does your gut instinct tell you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Have you ever had your heart broken before?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I mean, he's OK.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Is he heartbroken?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Yes, I was stunned.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Were you very saddened by what happened personally?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Yes, I shed a couple of tears.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Did you shed a tear?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, I've seen her several times.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Have you spoken to her since?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I think that there -- you know, I think -- I think the explanation probably has more to do with the fact that, you know, did it run its course and she didn't really love me.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "One that you believe?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Well, one of the two girls I'm seeing now is 27.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "But have you thought of trying somebody nearer your own age, Hef, in their 30s or something?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "To some extent, obviously, sure.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Do you feel -- do you feel conned?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "No, it's not humiliating.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "And is that -- is that even vaguely humiliating for someone like you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "It would have been worse if she'd waited to get married?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, Anna has been -- she is -- was going to be our maid of honor.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Who are they?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "She's on the -- our left.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "And she's on the left or right there?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Emotionally?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "The other is Shera.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Who's the other young lady?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "EFNER: Yes, that is correct.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "So am I right in thinking that you have replaced Crystal with two proper new girlfriends now?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Not too sorry, no.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "So, I mean, how sorry should people be feeling for you?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I am in better shape than I would have been if I'd been married.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "You've bounced back strongly?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Has the experience, to be serious for a moment, has it put you off ever getting married again?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "The girls are very, very protective.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "They were clearly no fans of hers, right?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I think so, yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "That Crystal had ulterior motives?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I really don't know.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Who is the other guy that you obliquely referred to?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I am prepared for that probability.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Would it really anger you if you discovered she was seeing somebody behind your back?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I think that is part of it.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "You think that's what happened?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I would say the great difference is that one thing, any girl who's ever been with me can say, quite frankly, is that I never played shady.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Yes, well, my first wife was a brunette.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Any comment?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "And she cheated on me right before we got married.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "And what happened?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, if I knew the answer to that one, I'd be much wiser than I am.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Why has America got itself into this hole,, do you think, financially?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "We didn't pay as we went.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "When you put your finger on the business model of America, incorporated, what are the problems?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I think it's the wrong attitude.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Has America got to go and do business?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes and entrepreneurial.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Do you think America should go back to being a manufacturing country at its heart?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Well, production where it works, and entrepreneurial.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Less consumer-led and more production?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "EFNER: Yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Lost a bit of the entrepreneurial zeal?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "I did to begin with.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Do you trust Obama to get it right?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Made me very sad.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "I find much of the circumstances very suspect.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Do you believe that could ever happen?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "It is amazing the number of people that have Tweeted me immediately afterward, asking whether or not we would do a pictorial on her, et cetera.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Would you ever countenance offering a \"Playboy\" cover to somebody like Casey Anthony?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "There are classic examples, as a matter of fact, historically in terms of a black Miss America that we didn't do a pictorial on, because she was a black Miss America and I knew that would hurt her, and other similar examples.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Even though you would know, instinctively, it would sell millions of copies?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it's entirely subjective.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Is it just your instinct tells you that it would be inappropriate?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "I have mixed feelings about that.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110714pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Presumably, it's all about glamour and sex and fun of your old club, right?", "qSentId": 712}]